



George P Mathew

Date of birth: 05/05/1999 | **Nationality:** Indian | **Gender:** Male | **Phone number:**

(+91) 9747130057 (Mobile) | **Email address:** georgepmathew424@gmail.com

Address: Pulinilkunnathil, Chachippunna, Punnala P O, Kollam, Punnala, Korala 680606, Pathanapuram, India (Homa)

Kerala, 689696, Pathanapuram, India (Home)

ABOUT ME

I am a Civil Engineer with experience in managing and supervising construction projects. I'm focused on applying my knowledge to real-world projects and am interested in continuing to learn and develop in the field of civil engineering.

WORK EXPERIENCE

■ BEST TRADING – PATHANAPURAM

BUSINESS ASSISTANT – 12/2023 – CURRENT

- Assisted customers with product inquiries, improving sales through personalized service and technical guidance.
- · Handled billing operations.
- Contributed to local marketing efforts including product promotions and flyer distribution.

III SG CONSTRUCTION COMPANY - MUMBAI, INDIA

JUNIOR ENGINEER - 07/02/2023 - 30/11/2023

- Supervised pile foundation work and finishing work of the building
- Coordinated with various teams to ensure project milestones were met
- · Assisted in solving on-site issues and ensuring project quality
- Maintained communication with contractors and suppliers

EXCEL PRECAST SOLUTIONS PVT LTD – BANGALORE, INDIA

GRADUATE ENGINEER TRAINEE – 01/10/2021 – 30/09/2022

- Managed the erection of wall panels, beams, and slabs
- Conducted grouting and repair work on precast wall panels
- · Assisted in quality checks of precast components
- Collaborated with the team to ensure timely completion of tasks

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

07/06/2017 - 29/07/2021 Marthandam, India

BE CIVIL ENGINEERING Mar Ephraem College Of Engineering And Technology

Website https://www.marephraem.edu.in/

2015 - 2017

GOVERNMENT OF KERALA, BOARD OF HIGHER SECONDARY EXAMINATIONS St. Thomas Higher Secondary School & Senior Secondary School

2014 - 2015

CENTRAL BOARD OF SECONDARY EDUCATION St. Thomas Higher Secondary School & Senior Secondary School

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): MALAYALAM

Other language(s): TAMIL | HINDI

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production Spoken interaction		า
ENGLISH	B2	C1	B2	B2	C1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

SKILLS

Microsoft Office package: Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access \mid Adobe illustrator, InDesign, Photoshop \mid Autodesk AutoCAD (2006/2017) \mid SkechUP